- Everyone in the back, into the kitchen. - Excuse me?
- 所有人都到后面去 进厨房去 - 不好意思?
- Let's go, move! - Ok, all right.
- 咱们走 快点! - 噢 好吧
Mr. Gazi, I was just about to call you.
Gazi先生 我刚刚还想给你打电话来着
I talked to Raman, he said I have more time. That's not what he told me.
- 我跟Raman谈过了 他说我的期限还没到 - 他可不是这么对我说的
He said I should come and break some bones.
他说我应该过来 给你点颜色瞧瞧
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on, hold on, no! Wait! no!
等等 等等 稍等 稍等!
C'mon, don't do this. Please.
拜托 别这样 求你了
Calm down, just... You don't have to do this, all right?
淡定淡定 只要...你不必这么做的 好嘛?
I can get you the money. Just give me one more day.
我会还你钱的 只要再给我一天时间就好
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第6集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第6集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：扫把不带星啊
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：瑜香 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：扫把不带星啊
- Good run? - Jesus!
- 跑得还行么? - 我了个去的!
You scared the hell out of me.
你差点吓得我尿裤子
You have any idea how easy it is to get in here?
你知道要进屋来有多容易吗
You should try locking your door for starters. Yeah, yeah.
- 最起码你得学会把门锁起来吧 - 嗯 嗯
What's going on? Rebecca called an early briefing.
- 发生什么事了? - Rebecca叫我们去参加早会
You weren't picking up so... I decided to come by.
你没接电话 所以...我想还是来找你吧
You thinking about putting some furniture in this place?
你有考虑给这儿添点家具吗
I got the important stuff. How long have you been here, four months?
- 重要的东西都在这儿了 - 你住这儿多久了 四个月?
- Six and a half. - Six and a half months?
- 六个半月 - 六个半月?
And you have one plant, and you killed it.
就只添了一棵植物 然后还被你弄死了
Look at that. Look, it's a metaphor.
你看呐 看看 这是个比喻
Just because you're divorced doesn't mean you have to live like a slob.
你离婚了 并不等于就要过的跟个懒鬼一样
Separated. All right? There's a big difference.
只是分居 好嘛? 区别大了去了
All right. I'm just saying, John.
好吧 我想说的是 John
This isn't a home, it's depressing.
这里根本就不像个家 这里很压抑
Does Emily stay here? Where... where does she sleep?
Emily住这儿吗 那她...要睡哪儿?
Alright. That's enough, okay. I'm going to have a shower.
好吧 够了 别说了 我去洗个澡
- Make yourself some coffee, if you want. - All right.
- 如果要喝咖啡的话 你自己弄吧 - 行
- Hey, look at this. - Who's that?
- 嗨 看看这个 - 那是谁?
He's been cracking her up for the last twenty minutes.
他已经在那儿拍了20分钟马屁了
You have any idea who that guy is? None.
- 你知道这家伙是谁吗 - 不知道
...they're pointed at you, so...
...他们指着你 然后...
All I remember is you were a sloppy drunk.
我只记得你当时彻底喝大了
- I was an exceptional drunk. - Oh. Okay, I remember it.
- 我那次喝得特别多 - 对 我记得
That you... uh, I remember shots of tequila lined up.
你喝了...我记得龙舌兰的杯子都能排成一行了
I remember, correct me if I'm wrong, lime green underwear.
我还记得...如果记错了你告诉我哈 你当时穿着石灰绿的内衣
- More of a minty green. - Oh, I see.
- 其实是薄荷绿 - 噢 明白了
I do remember you drinking me under the table, though..
我还记得 即使如此你还是让我 喝得躺到桌子底下去了
What's this, an early briefing?
这是在开早会吗
John, there you are, good.
John 你来了 很好
- This is Marcus Jakes, he's a U.C. - Right.
- 这位是Marcus Jakes 他是个卧底警察 - 没错
Hey. John Moreland, in the flesh.
你好 我是John Moreland 如假包换
- The stories I hear about you, brother. - How you doing?
- 我听说过你的事 老兄 - 你好吗
Jakes and I were in uniform together. Same division.
Jakes和我以前是同事 一个部门的
Small world.
这个世界真小
I used to make her laugh so hard that coffee would shoot out her nose.
我以前经常让她开怀大笑 笑到咖啡都能从鼻孔里喷出来
She still do that?
她现在还这样吗
- All the time. - Okay. So. Briefing.
- 一直如此 - 好的 那么 开简报会吧
- Right. - Yeah.
- 好的 - 嗯
Ali Raman, runs a protection racket.
Ali Raman 操控一个收保护费的团伙
Illegal gambling, torture, murder.
非法赌博 拷打 谋杀
He's got an underground fight club, it's pretty intense.
他有一家地下的搏击俱乐部 很热闹
Yeah, I've heard of this guy, he's a borderline psychopath.
嗯 我听说过这家伙 边缘性心理变态
Jakes has been deep undercover.
Jakes潜伏进这个组织很深了
- Eight months. - Cool.
- 八个月了 - 厉害
My path into Raman's operation has been through his lieutenant. A guy named Ric Gazi.
我渗透进Raman的组织是通过他的副手 一个叫Ric Gazi的家伙
- Oh. Look at that. - It's magic.
- 噢 看看呐 - 这是魔法
Ok, I'm in deep with Gazi... Worked my way onto his crew.
好吧 我跟Gazi的交情很深... 通过我的方式进入他的小圈子
And you've been doing what?
你是怎么做到的?
You know, collections. Trashing stores, intimidating folks, that kind of thing.
你知道的 收债 打砸商店 恐吓他人之类的
I could arrest Gazi right now, but he is not my focus.
我现在就可以逮捕Gazi 但他不是我的目标
I want this guy. I want Raman, I want the boss.
我想抓的是这家伙 我要抓到Raman 抓住老板
- Major Crimes is asking us to help out. - Why, where's your handler?
- 重案组要求我们帮忙 - 为什么 你的联系人呢
The handler was Stu Crowder, he's out of the picture.
联系人是Stu Crowder 这件事他不在其中
Out of the picture, what does that suppose to mean?
不在其中 这是什么意思?
What happened to him? Uh, whiskey...
- 他怎么了? - 那个 威士忌...
...happened to him. Followed by gin, followed by paint thinner,
喝多了 然后是杜松子酒 然后就是油漆稀释剂了 (酒精可用于油漆稀释剂)
if that's what he had around. After a while he just stopped checking in.
如果他手边有那个的话 一段时间之后 他就不再定期联系我了
I'd called for surveillance, and backup, I get nothing.
我要求进行监视 找支援 什么都没有
I was completely on my own.
所以完全靠我一个人
So, what can we do for you, Mr. Jakes?
那么 我们有什么能帮你的 Jakes先生?
My boy Gazi, he's got ambitions.
我的小伙伴Gazi 他可是野心勃勃
He's wants to take out Raman. He's planning a hit.
他想要取Raman而代之 他在策划一次行动
We can't let that happen.
我们不能让他得逞
- So we're going to get in front of it. - Mh-hmm...
- 所以我们要先下手为强 - 这个么...
You are going to be my old friend John the hit-man.
你会扮成我的老朋友 杀手John
I'm going to introduce you to Gazi.
我会把你介绍给Gazi
You're gonna meet him, you're gonna talk to him, you're gonna take the contract.
你跟他会面 跟他谈话 然后让他把这次任务指派给你
- And then we pick him up. - Conspiracy to murder, that's big.
- 然后我们实施抓捕 - 预谋杀人 这罪名可不小
Yeah, I need him out of the way. I need a clear shot at his boss.
是啊 我需要把他先踢出去 然后再好好收拾他老板
I want Raman in prison, not dead.
我想把Raman活着送进监狱
Alright, listen up. Our first step... Just wait a second.
- 好吧 听着 我们的第一步是... - 稍等一下
How do you know about this hit he's got planned? He told me.
- 你是怎么知道他的这个行动计划的? - 他告诉我的
So you didn't offer?
所以不是你提议的?
No, of course not.
不 当然不是
What's your point?
你想说什么?
My point is, is just I want to know what I'm walking myself into here.
我想说的是 我得知道自己要面对的是个什么情况
Make sure this meet is clean.
确保这次会面没有猫腻
Relax. I know what I'm doing. The job is solid.
放松 我知道自己在做什么 这趟活是板上钉钉的
Jesse, you'll cover things from the inside, you'll be a fighter, training at Raman's club.
Jesse 你从内部打掩护 你去当一名拳手 在Raman的俱乐部训练
You'll be our eyes in there.
你会是我们在那儿的眼线
I'm going to have to wire you.
我得给你装上窃听
With what you're wearing, I'm gonna have to do your chest.
根据你之后的穿着 我得把它装在你胸口
- Can you take your shirt off? - Yeah.
- 你能把上衣脱掉吗 - 好
Are you kidding me?
你不是吧?
What?
怎么了?
Nothing.
没事
Come here.
过来
Gazi will be at the club, that's where he does business.
Gazi在俱乐部 他通常在那里做生意
Jakes, you're gonna walk John inside, introduce him. We'll be recording everything.
Jakes 你陪John进去 介绍他 我们会录下全过程
As soon as Gazi offers John the contract, we got him.
一等Gazi把任务交给John 我们就行动
Alright, they just came in.
好的 他们刚进门
Jesse, make sure you keep them in sight. Copy that.
- Jesse 确保他们在你的视线内 - 收到
On the face of it is completely legit, but after hours it's a whole different thing.
这儿表面上是完全合法的 但是到了晚上就完全不同了
The gloves come off, bare knuckle fights. A lot of gambling, a lot of blood.
脱下手套 赤膊上阵 充满了赌博和血腥
- They never get shut down? - No, never.
- 他们从没被关闭过? - 没有 从来没有
Raman knows exactly who to pay off, and exactly how much.
Raman清楚应该打点谁 还很清楚要花多少钱打点
The guy in there right now, the guy behind me, green shirt,
在那儿的那个家伙 我身后的那个 绿衣服的
that's the trainer Duffy, Eli Duff. He runs all the fighters.
是教练Duffy  Eli Duff 他负责所有的拳手
Every single one of them does double duty as enforcers. The kid in there with him, that's Gavin.
他们每一个人都身兼拳手和打手 和他在一起的那孩子是Gavin
If you don't pay your debt, he comes by, he breaks your arms.
如果你不还债 他们就会出现 然后把你的手打断
Ok.
好
So, over there. That's my guy Gazi,
在那儿 我的小伙伴Gazi
Raman's second in command.
Raman的二把手
He wants Raman gone so he can take over the whole operation.
他想要除掉Raman这样他就能上位了 接手整个组织
He's a little paranoid, so don't take it personally.
他有点儿偏执 你别往心里去
Well, he's planning to kill his boss, I'd be paranoid too.
好吧 他正打算把自己的老板干掉 我要是他我也偏执了
They're approaching Gazi. There he is.
- 他们在靠近Gazi - 他在那儿
What... whoa, wait, wait, wait for it, wait.
什么...等等 等等 等一下
Chewy says he's sorry, won't be late again.
Chewy说他很抱歉 下次不会再迟了
Don't say I never gave you nothing.
别说我没给过你机会
Oh, this is my friend. This is the guy.
对了 这是我朋友 就是那一位
- The guy I told you about. - How you doing? John.
- 我跟你提起过的那位 - 你好吗 我是John
He does the thing, the service.
他干那一行的 提供服务
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我完全不知道你在说什么
What did I tell you? He hates new people, this guy.
我跟你说过吧? 这家伙他不喜欢新人
Gazi, we had the conversation, you wanted to meet a guy,
Gazi 我们之前聊过的 你想要见他
now you're meeting him.
现在他来了
- What's happening? - I don't know. Looks like a stand off.
- 发生什么了? - 我不知道 看上去像是没谈拢
You're imagining things, my friend. You need to walk away right now.
你这是在妄想 我的朋友 现在你应该离开了
I told him this was a bad idea.
我告诉过他这是个坏点子
- He's got zero judgment, this guy. - What are you talking about?
- 他一点判断力都没有 就这货 - 你在说什么呢?
You think he's going to discuss business in front of all these people? Come on.
你以为他会当着这么多人的面谈生意? 得了吧
Apologize. Come on, let's go.
抱歉 来吧 咱们走
You're killing me here, you know that?
你真是要了我的命了 你知道吗?
Tell him we're gonna meet somewhere else. Brickworks, north side.
告诉他我们在别的地方碰头 砖厂 北面
- Yes. - In the parking lot.
- 好 - 在停车场
Alright that'll work, that's good. I'll ask him.
好 这能行 不错 我去问问他
Brickworks, north side, parking lot.
砖厂 北面 停车场
Be there in twenty minutes, your last chance.
20分钟内到 最后的机会
Alright, they're on their way out.
好了 他们正走出去
When we're going to wait here in the car. Let Gazi come to us.
我们要在车里等 让Gazi来找我们
When he comes in, let him drive the conversation.
等他来了 让他来引导这次谈话
- Don't lead him, alright? - All right.
- 不要引导他 明白吗 - 明白
Maria and Danny are going to be at 2 o'clock running spin.
Maria和Danny会在2点钟方向
What's he thinking with these tinted windows,
他是怎么想的 这些都是有色玻璃
how are we going to see Gazi when he's in the backseat?
如果Gazi在后座的话 我们怎么可能看得见?
Rebecca will be in the lot behind us. She'll have eyes on the entrance.
Rebecca会停在我们后面 她能看到停车场的入口
Here's Rebecca.
Rebecca来了
Ok, she's in position.
好了 她就位了
It's good to see Rebecca, she looks good.
很高兴能见到Rebecca 她看上去很不错
You two getting along? Most of the time.
- 你们俩合得来吗 - 大多数时候
Yeah, she takes a while that one.
是啊 这方面她比较慢热
You two will be fine.
你们俩会合得来的
She's worth it. She's one of a kind, seriously.
她值得拥有 她是百里挑一的 我说真的
The best cop I've ever known.
我认识的最好的警察
John, Gazi's approaching the entrance.
John Gazi正在接近入口
Get ready.
准备好
We got eyes.
我们能看见
OK, here he is. We're good, Gazi's alone.
好了 他来了 不错 Gazi一个人来的
- John, do you have a clear view? - Yeah, we're good.
- John 你那儿看得清楚吗 - 嗯 看得清楚
- What is he doing? - Is he gonna get out?
- 他在干嘛? - 他到底要不要出来?
Relax. He's just being cautious.
放松 他只是比较警觉
Come on, Gazi.
快点 Gazi
Alright, here we go.
好了 来了
Shots fired, Rebecca Where's... where's the shooter?
- 有人开枪了 Rebecca - 枪手...枪手在哪儿?
There he is, by the warehouse. Daniel, stay with him.
- 在那儿 仓库那儿 - Daniel 追上他
I got him. I got him, he's headed south. We're in pursuit.
我看到他了 看到了 往南边去了 我们正追着
Shots fired. Brickworks, north side parking lot, send an ambulance.
有人开枪了 在砖厂 北面 停车场 派一辆救护车来
Alright, hold on.
好了 坚持住
All I'm saying is this whole thing is based on Jakes' information.
我要说的是 这一切都是建立在Jakes的消息之上的
Jakes' judgment, all right?
是Jakes的判断 明白吗
If he was doing his job, he would have known about the hit.
如果他有好好干活 他就应该知道这次袭击的
- But you're not placing blame. - No I'm not placing blame.
- 但是你这不是在责怪谁 对么 - 不 我不是在责怪谁
Rebecca, wait, okay?
Rebecca 等等 好嘛?
I've worked with guys like this before, all right?
我之前也跟这样的家伙合作过 明白吗
- They fly by the seat of their pants. - And you don't?
- 毫无依据就盲目靠直觉行事 - 难道你不是么?
If Gazi was exposed... he should have been on top of that...
如果Gazi暴露了...那他就是嫌疑最大的那个人...
He didn't know it was going to happen, John. You would have made the same call.
他不知道事情会变成这样 John 你也会做出同样的判断的
I know this guy's a friend of yours, all right,
我知道这家伙是你的朋友 好嘛
but maybe you've got a blind spot for this guy. Do you ever think of that?
但是也许你对他有盲点 你就从来没想过吗
He's a good cop, you need to back off.
他是个好警察 你少罗嗦
Ric Gazi was DOA at Mount Sinai.
Ric Gazi在Mount Sinai当场身亡
Homicide wants you to call.
凶杀组让你打电话给他们
I'm sure they do.
我就知道他们会这么要求的
You're gonna have to give a full statement. We all are.
你得给出一个完整的声明 我们都是
- Shooter? - He got away.
- 凶手呢 - 他逃走了
I had no idea guys, I swear to God.
我真的什么都不知道 伙计们 我对天发誓
So, what happened. Raman caught wind of the hit?
所以 发生了什么 Raman突然灵光一现
Found out his boy's coming after him, got there first?
发现他的手下要干掉他 于是先下手为强?
- Yeah, must have been. - Could have been a pre-emptive strike.
- 是啊 一定是这样的 - 也许就是先发制人
It means you might be done, Jakes. Too bad. That's eight months work down the drain.
那就意味着你也完了 Jakes 太糟了 这八个月的努力都付诸东流了
Or maybe it works in my favor.
也许这正帮了我一个忙
It's an opportunity, maybe it's a chance to move up.
这是个机会 也许是往上走的机遇
How do you figure that?
你是怎么得出这个结论的?
You're one of Gazi's boys, Raman's going to smell you a mile away.
你是Gazi的手下 你有任何风吹草动Raman都会知道的
All I gotta do is make a move, guys.
我要做的只是一步而已 伙计们
I just gotta send a message. Show Raman that I'm loyal, that I wasn't involved.
我只要发个信息 让Raman知道我很忠诚 我并没有参与这件事
John could be right. You could be next in line for a bullet.
John可能是对的 你可能就是下一个被干掉的对象
And if my guys are with you, they're in danger too.
如果我的人和你在一起 那他们也有危险了
We need to make sure Jakes is safe. That's our next move.
我们得确保Jakes是安全的 这是咱们的下一步行动
We could put Jesse in as a fighter slash enforcer, maybe?
我们可以让Jesse去当拳手兼打手 也许?
He's already been in the club. He's established.
他已经在俱乐部里了 已经是一分子了
John?
John?
Yeah, he could be looking for extra cash. Jakes, you can walk him in, make the intro.
没错 就说他想要赚外快 Jakes 你可以陪他一起去 给他引荐一下
He could be one of your boys. It'll give us a sense.
- 他可能会成为其中的一位打手 - 这样我们就能知道消息了
If anyone looks at you sideways, Jakes, that's it, we're out.
有人看你不爽 Jakes 那就不干了 咱们退出
Copy that. Kid, I hope you know how to fight.
收到 小孩儿 我希望你知道如何打拳击
Raw talent, quick learner.
天生的材料 学得也很快
You need a guy to do collections, he can do that too.
你要找个人去收债 他可以帮上忙
You said you were looking for new people. How you doing?
- 你说过你正在招新人的 - 你好吗
Where'd you find him? This girl I know, he's her kid brother.
- 你在哪儿找到他的? - 我认识的一个女孩儿 是她弟弟
She's insane, she thinks he's the next big thing.
她是个疯婆子 觉得他会成为下一个巨星
Maybe she's right.
也许她是对的
Yeah, listen kid, this is Duffy, you do exactly what he says, all right?
是啊 听着 孩子 这位是Duffy 他让你做什么你就做什么 懂吗
Yeah.
明白
Throw him in there with Gavin, see what he does.
让他跟Gavin比比 看看他的身手
First spar doesn't go to one of my boys.
第一场不跟我的手下比
It goes to me.
跟我比
Good luck, kid.
祝你好运 孩子
Alright, here we go.
好了 来吧
Take it easy on him, Duff.
对他下手别太重了 Duff
Come on, Jesse, here we go, make this count.
来吧 Jesse 加油 抓紧时间
Keep it together. Let's go, let's go.
稳住 加油 加油
Watch his feet, c'mon.
看着他的步伐 加油
That's it, that's it, wait for an opening.
对了 对了 等待机会
That's alright, you got this, c'mon!
没错 机会来了 上啊!
Shake it off.
摆脱他
Come on, stay on him. Let's go, let's go.
来吧 盯住他 出拳 出拳
Alright, Duffy, I think you made your point.
好了 Duffy 我想你的意思很明确了
Alright, you can let him up I think. He can't breathe.
好了 你该让他起来了 他都快窒息了
Let him up, man. What are you doing?
让他起来吧 伙计 你在干嘛呢?
Your boy's okay. Tell him to come see me later.
你的人不错 让他等会儿来见我
You made the right choice, by the way.
你做出了正确的选择 顺便说一句
You had a front cross. You saw it, but you didn't take it.
你有机会打击他的前胸的 你看到了 但是你放弃了
You let Duffy smoke you. You noticed?
- 你让Duffy轻易把你撂倒了 - 你注意到了?
I did the same thing, my first time.
我跟你一样 第一次的时候
You're gonna do just fine here.
你在这儿会没事的
Come on.
来吧
What'd I tell you? I'm safe, we're good to go.
我说什么来着? 我是安全的 我们可以继续进行了
- What have you got? - All right. Bear with me.
- 你有什么主意? - 好吧 听我说
Raman is in the business, among other things, of collecting debts, right?
Raman主要的生意 跟其他的事情相比 主要是收债 对吗
And sometimes he buys a debt from someone else.
有时候他会从别人手里把债权买过来
For example, you're a gambler. You're Gambler Dan.
比如 你是个赌棍 你叫赌棍Dan
And you owe John here, two-fifty, three hundred grand. You're not paying.
然后你欠了这位John二十五万 三十万债 然后你不还
And Gentleman John here is an old friend of mine from way back, you know, he's not a violent man.
然后这位绅士John是我多年前的老朋友 你知道的 他不是个暴力的人
He can't go around breaking people's fingers,
他不好意思为了要债打断别人的手指头
he doesn't have the stomach for it.
他没有种做这个
So I bring Raman the debt, and he buys it for, say, I don't know, 50 grand.
所以我找到Raman 他买下债权 比如花个五万块
He's like a collection agent.
他就好比是讨债公司
Now Gambler Dan owes him. And if he doesn't pay, his legs get broken.
现在赌棍Dan就欠他钱了 如果他不还 就会被打断腿
But we've already established, John as a hit-man.
但是我们已经安排他出过场了 说John是个杀手
But no one knows that.
但是没人知道这件事
They only saw him in the club. So why was he in the club?
他们只看到他出现在俱乐部 那他去俱乐部是干嘛的?
- You were introducing him to Gazi. - Right.
- 你把他介绍给了Gazi - 没错
Because of the debt Gazi was going to buy. And now that Gazi's dead...
因为本来Gazi是打算买下那笔债权的 但是现在Gazi死了...
You're going to take it all the way up to Raman.
你就会把生意都直接介绍给Raman
Yes... This is the move I've been waiting to make.
是的...我一直一来就在等待这样的机会
Raman goes after gambler Dan...
Raman去找赌棍Dan...
And just as he's about to break some fingers...
然后就在他打算打断他的手指前...
In comes the dream team. Guns a'blazin. Ready to make some arrests.
梦幻支队如梦幻般的降临 火力全开 准备逮捕吧
Loan sharking, extortion, assault.
放高利贷 敲诈勒索 暴力袭击
Guys, what do you think?
伙计们 觉得如何?
It's not terrible.
还不赖
Thoughts?
有什么想法么?
Let's do it. Let's take it for a spin.
就这么办吧 咱们出去转转
Yes?
什么事?
Marcus.
Marcus
This is John Bain.
这位是John Bain
Pleasure. Please sit.
很荣幸见到你 请坐
Marcus, has told me about your predicament.
Marcus把你的困境告诉我了
I love my sister.
我很爱我的妹妹
Only she has terrible taste in men.
只不过她挑男人的品位真的很差
He's a gambler, they were together for two years.
他是个赌鬼 他们在一起两年了
He stole three hundred thousand from her.
他从她那儿偷了三十万
And when she found out, he became very violent.
等她发现了以后 他就变得非常的暴力
He almost killed her.
他差点就把她弄死了
And now you want your money back.
现在你想要拿回你的钱
I want him to pay.
我想让他付出代价
I want your personal attention on this. I hear you're the best.
我希望你能高度重视这件事 我听说你是最好的
Can you do it?
你能做到吗
Possibly.
也许
I'll need time to have Gavin check him out.
我需要时间 让Gavin先去查查他的底细
Whatever you need. He lives at 19 West Elm Street.
随你怎样都行 他住在West Elm街19号
John has a special request.
John有个特别的要求
Go ahead.
请说
I want to be there when you do it.
你动手的时候 我希望能在场
When you collect.
当你收债的时候
I want to look into his eyes, when you're making him pay.
我想要看着他的眼睛 就在你让他付出代价的时候
Hey. John asked me to check into Jakes' files.
嗨 John让我查看了一下Jakes的那些档案
Really?
真的?
Yeah, and I think we might have a problem.
嗯 我想我们可能有麻烦了
So I've been pulling all of Jakes' case work from the last eight months. And it's full of holes.
所以我调出了过去八个月Jakes经手的所有档案 到处都是漏洞
I'm not surprised, the handler was AWOL...
我不觉得奇怪 因为他的联系人擅离职守...
Yeah, I'm not so sure it's just the handler.
好吧 我不太确定只是联系人的问题
I mean, he's got paper, just not a lot of evidence.
我是说 他只有书面材料 没有什么实证
There's no video, there's no audio.
没有录影也没有录音
His hand-written notes are sketchy at best.
他手写的那些说明 连草书都够不上
There's nothing here that would stand up in court.
这里的东西没有一件是可以作为呈堂证供的
And there's this woman, Abi Rand.
然后还有这个女人 Abi Rand
Jakes has been using her as a CI. Former heroin addict.
Jakes把她作为线人 一位前海洛因成瘾者
Her information hasn't led to a single arrest, and yet he keeps paying her.
她所提供的消息没有帮助我们执行过一起逮捕 而他还继续付钱给她
Thousands of dollars for nothing.
几千块钱付诸东流
Look, this all could have an explanation,
听着 这些可能都有合理的解释
but if Jakes is lying to us, if he's out of control...
但如果Jakes在对我们说谎 如果他已经失去了控制...
So he's sleeping with his C.I. Probably, yeah.
- 所以他跟他的线人上床了 - 很有可能 是的
I'm going to bring her in, talk to her.
我会把她带回来问话
- Have you looked at the case work? - It's a mess.
- 你有看过那些书面报告吗 - 一团糟
It could be the handler. You're going to blame the handler on this one?
- 可能是联系人的问题 - 你打算把责任都归结于联系人?
I know Jakes, he would never jeopardize a case like this.
我了解Jakes 他永远不会像这样来危害一个案子的
Rebecca, you knew him fifteen years ago.
Rebecca 你认识的是十五年前的他
If you ask me, I think you should shut down this whole thing right now.
如果你问我的意见 我觉得你应该立刻叫停所有的行动
Maybe he's been in too long...
也许他已经太久...
Rebecca?
Rebecca?
He believed in me, John.
他信任我 John
He was the first.
他是第一个
He use to say, "I'd follow you anywhere. "
他以前常说 不管你去哪里 我都跟着你
"I'd walk off a cliff for you. "
哪怕两肋插刀也在所不惜
I'm giving him the benefit of the doubt on this.
关于这个疑点 我倾向于相信他
- What's the C.I.'s name? - Abi.
- 那个线人叫什么名字? - Abi
Alright, when she comes in, Maria should talk to her,
好吧 等她来了 让Maria跟她谈
not you.
你不行
We need to know we can trust Jakes.
我们得知道Jakes值得信任
Until then, I'll look after things myself, all right?
在那之前 由我来负责一切 好么?
I'll cover Jesse at the set-up house. Soon as Daniel checks out Raman, we move.
我会在目标位置掩护Jesse 一旦Daniel发现Raman 我们就行动
Put Jakes' play in action, Gambler Dan.
执行Jakes的计划 赌棍Dan
You want to head over, take a look inside?
你想要靠过去么 进屋里看看?
Not yet. We're gonna sit tight. See who comes and goes.
不急 我们先坐会儿 看看都有什么人出入
So what happens if he won't pay? Rough him up a little?
万一他不还钱怎么办? 让他吃点苦头?
We're just doing research, that's all.
我们只是在做调查 仅此而已
Alright, they're in place. Let's give it a few minutes.
好了 他们到位了 咱们等几分钟
I'm ready. Just say the word.
我准备好了 就等下令了
I'm just trying to figure this whole thing out.
我只是想要弄清楚事情的来龙去脉
So, the boss is Raman. And Gazi, he got shot, he's dead.
所以 老板是Raman 然后Gazi被击中了 死了
But then, Duffy, he's the one who gives you the orders, right?
然后是Duffy 他是给你下令的人 对吗
You ask a lot of questions.
你问得太多了
Whatever, we don't have to talk.
好吧 我们不是非得聊天的
Okay, Daniel. Any time.
好了Daniel 可以过来了
Here he is.
他来了
Sweet car.
车很不错嘛
That's a hundred grand easy, right there.
几十万 唾手可得 就在那儿
Yeah, that's him, that's our guy. No question
对 就是他 就是我们要找的人 毫无疑问
- Are you kidding me? - What?
- 这不是跟我开玩笑吧? - 怎么了?
Hang on a sec.
稍等一会儿
What's wrong? I don't believe it.
- 真不敢相信
- That guy arrested me. - What?
- 那家伙逮捕过我 - 什么?
Like seven, eight years ago. That guy's a cop!
大概七八年前 那家伙是个警察!
What? You're sure?
什么? 你确定?
My first bust, man. I'll never forget his face.
我第一次被捕 伙计 永远忘不了他那张脸
- Daniel, you just got made. - You're kidding me.
- Daniel 你刚刚暴露了 - 不是吧
You're busted. Stay in the house, stay out of sight.
你被认出来了 待在屋里 待在视线以外
Man, what are the friggin' odds?
伙计 这几率得是多小啊?
So what are we gonna do?
那我们现在要做什么?
What do you think we're gonna do? We're going to tell the boss.
你觉得我们应该做什么? 当然是报告给老板啊
Son of a...
狗娘养的...
Ah, come on...
得了吧...
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
You want to tell me where I am?
你要告诉我身处何地吗
Abi, I'm Detective Constable Cortez.
Abi 我是Constable Cortez探员
Am I under arrest?
我被捕了?
Are you a confidential informant for Marcus Jakes?
你是Marcus Jakes的线人吗
Is this your C.I. number?
这是不是你的线人编号?
Was I supposed to memorize it?
我还得记住这个?
What about this, is that your signature?
那这个呢 是不是你的签名?
Where's Marcus?
Marcus在哪儿?
These are all payments made to you,
这些都是付给你的钱
in exchange for information. False information by the looks of it.
用来交换消息 用面上看全都是些无效的消息
But he kept paying you.
但是他依然付给你钱
Are you sleeping with him, Abi?
你是不是跟他上床了 Abi?
He's not paying me for sex.
他不是因为性才付给我钱的
- Is Marcus Jakes your boyfriend? - So what if he is?
- Marcus Jakes是你男朋友吗 - 如果是又怎样?
I get it, Abi. You probably thought you'd never get in trouble for this.
我明白了Abi 可能你觉得自己永远不会因此而深陷囹圄
I mean he's a cop, right?
因为他是个警察 对吧?
Here's the thing, though, it's bogus information.
事实是 这些都是假消息
It won't hold up in court. You both knew it.
在法庭上是站不住脚的 你们俩都心知肚明
That's an offence.
这是犯罪
I should arrest you, right now.
我可以逮捕你 就现在
- I want to talk to Marcus. - That's not happening.
- 我要跟Marcus讲话 - 这不可能
I can't go to jail, okay? I can't. I can't do that.
我不能去坐牢 明白吗 我不能 不能这么做
I need to show you something. Do you know who this man is?
我有东西要给你看 你认识这个男人吗
Abi?
Abi?
Can you tell me his name.
你能告诉我他的名字么?
That's Chip.
那是Chip
- That's my ex. - Do you know who did this to him?
- 我前男友 - 你知道是谁对他做的这些吗
He was stalking me, he wouldn't leave me alone.
他之前在跟踪我 怎么甩也甩不掉
Abi. He almost died.
Abi 他差点就死了
Who did this? Who was it?
谁干的? 是谁?
It was Marcus. Marcus did it.
是Marcus Marcus干的
Chip came by my apartment and Marcus just lost it.
Chip来我的公寓找我然后Marcus就失控了
I thought he was gonna kill him.
我以为他会杀了他
What are you doing man, what are you doing here?
你在干嘛 老兄 你怎么来这儿了?
- Hey, can I come in? - Yeah, come on in.
- 嗨 我能进来吗 - 能啊 请进
Uh... Give me a minute.
那个...给我一分钟
- Alright. - Yeah.
- 好的 - 嗯
- Nice digs. - Yeah, it does the job, right?
- 这地方不错 - 是啊 物尽其用 对吧?
This place wired?
这地方有装窃听吗
Bedroom's on the fritz, but you know...
卧室的坏了 不过你知道...
Yeah.
是啊
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 给你 - 谢谢
So you had a late night last night?
你昨晚睡得很晚?
What are we doing here, what's going on?
我们在这干嘛 出什么事了?
Rebecca's worried about the case.
Rebecca很担心这个案子
She wants you to come in.
她想让你去一趟
What else is new? She loves to worry, that girl.
这都算事儿? 她就喜欢瞎担心 那姑娘
That what you came by, to tell me? Could've just called.
你就为了这个过来一趟 为了通知我? 打个电话就行了
- Your phone's off. - I would've got the message.
- 你的电话关机了 - 我能收到短信的
So how's Danny-boy? How's our play shaking out?
Danny那边怎么样了? 咱们的计划进行得如何?
Daniel...
Daniel...
got made.
暴露了
- He, what? - Yup.
- 他什么? - 没错
- What did he do? - The muscle guy, Gavin.
- 他做了什么? - 那个肌肉男 Gavin
Turns out Daniel arrested him back in the day.
结果发现Daniel之前逮捕过他
- You're kidding me. - Nope.
- 你开玩笑吧 - 没有
That's just bad luck, that's what that is.
运气真差 真不走运
Seems to happen a lot on this case.
这个案子似乎总是运气很差
Let me ask you something.
我来问问你吧
If I were to go through this whole place, what kind of contraband would I find?
如果我把这个地方翻个底儿掉 我能找到多少违禁品?
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
Jakes, I've been here. I've done all this.
Jakes 我也是过来人 这些我都干过
Okay? I know the temptations.
明白吗 我知道那种诱惑
I must be good if I'm fooling you.
如果我有本事骗你的话 说明我能力还挺强的
You're falling for the look, man. The props.
你就是上了表象的当 那些小道具
I'm squeaky clean. You know what, John?
我一清二白 你知道吗 John
I would have thought you of all people would know what I'm doing here.
我还以为在这些人里面 你会是最明白我在做什么的人
I had to forget everything, but who I was.
我得忘记所有的一切 我的过去
Just to be this guy.
来扮演这个家伙
I watch guys get beaten every day and I just gotta stand there.
我每天都看到有人被揍 而我只能站在那里
You think that's fun for me?
你觉得这样对我来说很好玩?
I'm doing police work, are you going to help me or what?
我在执行警务 你到底是帮还是不帮我?
We talked to Abi. We brought her in.
我们跟Abi聊过了 把她带去了办公室
She told us the full extent.
她把一切都告诉我们了
She's prepared to testify.
她愿意作证
- The full extent of what? - You've been collecting debts.
- 一切的什么? - 你也参与了收债
You've been there when guys have gotten beaten.
当人们被揍时 你就在那儿
And you haven't just been watching, you've been doing it yourself.
你做的不仅仅是看 你还自己动手
No no no, that's the cover, it's not real, she doesn't understand
不 不 不 那只是装样子的 不是真的 她不明白
- Guys... - You've funneling cash to your C.I.
- 伙计们... - 你把钱都漏给了你的线人
You've been making money and not reporting it.
你一直在赚钱 然后还没有上报
- That's not true. - You know me, you know what I'm like.
这不是真的 你了解我的 你知道我是什么样的人
If it's true, I'm gonna find out.
如果这是真的 我会找出来的
I've been working this case for eight months.
我为了这个案子已经忙了八个月了
I dream of this, why would I put that in jeopardy?
这个案子是我的理想 我为什么要把它置于险境?
You like the lifestyle you like playing the part.
你喜欢这种生活方式 你喜欢假扮其他人
You don't want to leave it.
你不想离开
Is that what you think, Rebecca?
你是这么想的么 Rebecca?
Is that what this guy's telling you?
这家伙就是这么对你说的?
I swear to God, Marcus, I don't know what to think.
我对天发誓 Marcus 我不知道我该相信什么
Okay, this guy John-boy, I've heard a lot of stories.
好吧 这个家伙 John 我也听过他不少事
You don't think he bent the rules sometimes?
你觉得他是那种守规矩的人?
Okay look, this guy was abusive.
好吧 听着 这家伙当时口出狂言
He wouldn't leave her alone, I was worried for her.
他不肯对她放手 我很担心她
The case is good.
案子没问题
So what they know Daniel's a cop? That's workable.
就算他们知道了Daniel是警察又怎样? 照样说得通的
We could use that, he's not the first cop to owe a debt.
我们可以利用这一点 他又不是第一个欠债的警察
They'll never guess that's our cover. Rebecca, look at me.
他们永远都想不到这是我们的掩护 Rebecca 看着我
Come on, you know me, you know I wouldn't do this.
别这样 你了解我的 你知道我不会这么做的
I know who you were.
我了解的是以前的你
I need it.
我需要它
I need this Raman guy, he is a scumbag.
我需要扳倒Raman 他是个混蛋
And he ruins people's lives.
他毁灭别人的生活
I need something good to come out of all this.
我需要有好的结果
Don't.. Don't turn me into the guy...
别把我变成那种...
The cop who goes off the rails, and blows the big case.
那种走上歪路的警察 搞砸了大案子
Don't do it to me.
别这么对我
Can you give us a minute?
你能给我们一分钟么?
Yeah, yeah.
好 好
This guy Raman, he's vicious, he beats people up for a living.
这个叫Raman的家伙 他很恶毒 靠着殴打他人为生
He killed someone right in front of us.
他在我们眼皮子底下干掉了一个人
We need to get him, Rebecca.
我们得抓住他 Rebecca
Look, Jakes is on the edge, he has to be, it's what got him close to Raman.
听着 Jakes现在在悬崖边上 他必须如此 才能让他接近Raman
I think Jakes can do it.
我觉得Jakes能行
Really? After all this?
真的? 在发生了这么多以后?
You're going to put your life in his hands?
你要把自己的性命交到他手上?
You know as well as I do, that could be me outside that door right now..
你我都清楚 此刻在那扇门外的那个人可能是我的...
You believed in this guy. Let's give him a chance to redeem himself.
你相信这个人 咱们给他一个挽救自己的机会吧
Let's take Raman down.
咱们把Raman扳倒吧
So the good news is, Gavin doesn't remember your name, just your face.
好消息是 Gavin不记得你的名字了 只认得你的脸
Say hello to Daniel Winacott.
跟Daniel Winacott问个好吧
You're part of Guns and Gangs, just like the real Daniel.
你既混警队又混黑社会 就跟真实生活中的Daniel差不多
And after a couple years, you blew it. Infractions, bad performance reports,
几年之后 你搞砸了 违纪行为 工作表现很差
caught in a few gambling dens and then down-graded to a desk job.
几次被抓到赌博 然后被降级到文职工作
- So, I'm a file-clerk. - With a temper.
- 所以我是个文员 - 是脾气火爆的文员
And a gambling problem, you just can't resist a big fight.
还嗜赌 你就是忍不住要把事情闹大
Listen, you think this is going to work?
听着 你真觉得这事儿能行?
Raman deals with cops all the time, probably some of his best clients.
Raman总是跟警察打交道 有些指不定是他的重点客户呢
OK, It's fight night at Raman's club.
好了 在Raman的俱乐部举行的搏击之夜
Daniel, you're there to bet on the fight, and Maria, you're his new girlfriend.
Daniel 你去那里参与赌博 还有Maria 你是他的新女朋友
Jakes and John, you're gonna make contact with Raman,
Jakes和John 你们去跟Raman联系
and deliver Gambler Dan right to him.
然后把赌棍Dan送上门去
All Raman has to do is try and collect and we got him, we'll take him down.
Raman要做的只是收债 然后被我们抓到 就可以一网打尽了
Yo, focus man, I need you here.
嗨 注意力集中 我这儿需要你
- How's our boy doing? - To be honest, a bit shaky.
- 他怎么样? - 老实说 有点紧张
But he's obsessed with Raman. He'll get through it.
但是他一心想要抓住Raman 他会坚持下来的
- That Rebecca? She worried about me? - She's fine.
- 是Rebecca打来的? 她担心我? - 她没事
- Is that the best you can do? - Come on, tell me.
你就只能做到这样吗 少来了 告诉我吧
- Jakes, we're wired. - I don't care about the wire.
- Jakes 我们装了兼听 - 我才不在乎什么兼听
Give it to me straight, brother John. Is this my last day on the job?
有话直说吧 John老兄 今天是不是我最后一天开工?
This is our last chance at this case.
今晚是这个案子的最后一次机会
I mean as a cop. She's gonna take my badge, isn't she?
我是说作为一名警察 她会拿走我的警徽 是么?
That's up to you. Look, we'll talk about that tomorrow.
这取决于你 听着 咱们明天再谈这事
Tonight, let's just focus on getting the bad guys, all right?
今晚 咱们集中精力抓坏人 好么?
Rebecca wouldn't put you in play if she didn't think you could do this.
如果Rebecca觉得你做不到 是不会安排你参加行动的
You don't know Becks like I do.
你不像我那样了解Becks
Once you lose her trust, it's over. Right, Rebecca?
一旦你失去她的信任 就完了 对吗 Rebecca?
Well you're going to have to earn it back. Jakes, you are good at this job.
所以你得赢回信任 Jakes 这任务你做得很好
You just got to remind her that, alright?
你只需要提醒她这一点 好吗
Okay? Okay?
好吗 行吗
Yeah, yeah, okay.
好 好 没问题
Heads up. Here comes the target.
注意了 目标出现
Imagine my surprise when I discovered that the man
想象一下当我发现你让我去讨债的那个对象
you asked me to collect from is a cop.
居然是个警察时 我有多吃惊
He is, I should have mentioned that to you. I didn't want you to say no.
他是 我应该告诉你的 但我不想被你拒绝
Did you know about this, Marcus? Did you know?
你知道这件事吗 Marcus? 你知道吗
It's my fault I didn't even tell him.
是我不好 我甚至都没有告诉他
Look, this cop a screw-up. He has no friends.
听着 这个警察是个废人 他没有朋友
There will be no payback. You have my guarantee.
不会有人来报复 我向你保证
He's over there at the bar right now.
他就在吧台那边
He's with his new girlfriend.
和他的新女朋友在一起
You brought him here.
你把他带到这儿来了
I brought him to the fight as a peace offering.
我带他来看拳赛 作为和解
Trust me, he has absolutely no idea you're about to collect on his debt.
相信我 他完全不知道你会去问他讨债
Look, you're going to make a lot of money tonight, my friend.
听着 今晚你会赚上一大笔钱的 我的朋友
And you're going to have me to thank for that.
并且你会因此而感谢我
Let's do it right now, I'll call him over.
咱们现在就动手 我去叫他过来
No, leave him there for a minute, he's fine.
不用了 让他在那儿待着吧 他挺好的
He's enjoying himself. My problem is this.
他正享受着呢 我的问题是
I don't like police.
我不喜欢警察
And to be perfectly honest, I'm starting to have an uneasy feeling about you, Jakes.
并且说实话 我开始对你有种 很不自在的感觉了 Jakes
- What are you talking about? - And I always listen to that feeling.
- 你在说什么呢 - 而且我一直都会听从自己的感觉
What's he doing?
他在干什么?
Stop, why are you killing this?
别说了 你为什么要中断此事?
This is not happening. I'm sorry, Jakes.
今晚不会发生了 抱歉 Jakes
Not tonight. Enjoy the fight.
今晚不会 好好看比赛吧
You and your friend.
你和你的朋友
- That's it? He can't just walk away. - He can and he just did.
- 就这样? 他不能就这样一走了之 - 他可以 而且刚刚做了
Rebecca, I think we're done here.
Rebecca 我想这里已经结束了
You want to give him some time, circle back?
你想再给他点时间 也许会再回来?
No, there's no point. It's over. He just closed the door.
不 没意义了 结束了 他刚刚把门关上了
Come on, are you kidding me? You're just giving up?
得了吧 开玩笑吧? 你就这样放弃了?
Calm down Jakes, we're done.
冷静点 Jakes 结束了
So what? We're just shutting down?
接下去怎样? 咱们就这么结束了?
Let's pack it up.
准备收工吧
Here we go, boys.
准备好了 小伙子们
No head butts, eye gouging, groin attacks,
不许撞头 抠眼睛 打腹股沟
or head kicking to a grounded opponent.
也不许在对方倒地后踢他的头
- Alright, so that's it I guess. - Next time, right?
- 好吧 我看就这样了 - 下次了 对吗
I'll see you back at the shop.
我们回店里碰头
Okay, but I'm staying for the fight.
好的 但是我要留下来看比赛
What do you wanna do, wanna watch the fight?
你打算干什么 看比赛?
It's not over.
这事儿还没完
Jakes!
Jakes!
You think you can just walk away? You think we're done?
你觉得可以就这么一走了之? 你觉得咱们就算完了?
Come here!
过来!
Where do you go?Where do you go?
你要去哪儿?
Jakes.
Jakes
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
He's unarmed. He's going to tell us everything.
- 他没有武器了 - 他会告诉我们所有的事
Every crime, every detail.
每一次犯罪 每一个细节
Or I'm going to put a bullet in him.
否则我就把子弹送进他的脑袋
Hey, where's John? Have you seen him?
嗨 John去哪儿了? 你见到他了吗
No, and no Jakes.
没有 Jakes也不见了
- You think this is gonna work? - He's gonna confess.
- 你觉得这样会管用? - 他会反水的
He's gonna say we beat it out of him.
他会说我们把他暴打了一顿
And then we're gonna deny it.
然后我们会否认
What do you mean "we"?
你说"我们"是什么意思?
I, mean you and me. You're gonna get my back.
我 还有你 你会罩着我的
- You want me to lie for you? - Yes.
- 你想让我为你撒谎? - 没错
Eight months, John, I've been after this guy for eight months.
八个月了 John 我查这个家伙有八个月了
I'm not just gonna let him go. If you're not up for it, you leave.
我不会就这么让他脱身的 你要么加入 要么走人
Wake up!
醒醒!
Alright, Jakes. Come on, don't do this.
好了 Jakes 来吧 别这么做
I'm gonna back you up on this one, okay?
这个人的事我罩着你 行吗
We'll say he came after you, it was self-defense.
我们就说他找上了你 然后是自卫
You will not be charged.
你不会被起诉的
But after that, Jakes, you've got to walk away from this one right now.
但是之后 Jakes 你得离开 远离这个人
Right now, you need to walk away.
就是现在 你得离开这儿
Wake up!
醒醒!
Maria, what's going on in there?
Maria 里面发生什么事了?
- Jakes and John, where are they? - We left them watching the fight.
- Jakes和John去哪儿了? - 我们让他们留下看拳赛了
- What about Raman? - He's not here either.
- 那Raman呢 - 他也不在
Find them.
找到他们
We gotta split up.
我们分头找
I've been where you are. All right?
我是过来人 明白么?
Thanks to this job... I've racked up a divorce,
感谢这份工作...帮我走到了离婚的边缘
I got a bleak apartment I can barely unpack,
我有一间阴冷的公寓 我都没办法收拾好
I lie awake in my bed at night full of anger, full of this constant rage.
我整夜都躺在床上 充满愤怒 总是充满了怒火
Good for you.
挺好的
Awww, there he is!
啊哈 他醒了!
Wait, Jakes, I get it, all right? Oh no, you don't get it.
- 等等 Jakes 我懂了 行么? - 不 你不懂
This guy tortures people, and takes pleasure from doing it!
这家伙折磨他人 并且以此为乐!
And he's gonna say it, into the phone or I'm gonna put a bullet in his brain.
他要么对着这个电话 都说出来 要么我就让他脑袋开花
Talk, tell it! Tell me how you torture people!
说 快说! 说你是怎么折磨别人的!
You're right. This guy is scum.
你是对的 这家伙就是个混蛋
- Talk! - He's an animal, he deserves it.
- 快说! - 他是个畜生 他罪有应得
Okay, you could kill him right now, no one would shed a tear.
好吧 现在你可以把他杀了 没有人会流一滴眼泪的
Let me tell you something...
我要告诉你的是...
if you do that, if you shoot him,
如果你这么做 如果你对他开枪
you will be lost, my friend.
那么你就会彻底迷失 我的朋友
You are done.
你就完蛋了
You will never come back from that, ever again.
你再也无法回头了 永远不能
You understand me?
你明白我说的话吗
Jakes,
Jakes
right now you are standing on the edge.
此时此刻你正站在悬崖边上
You need to step back now. Just one step back.
现在 你需要往后退了 退一步
Come on, I'm right here.
来吧 我就在这儿
I'm not forcing you.
我不是在逼你
Come on.
来吧
You gotta step back.
你得往后退一步
- You're gonna charge him? - I'm gonna try.
- 你会起诉他吗 - 我尽量
- Jakes. - You need to arrest me.
- Jakes - 你得逮捕我
- You need to take me in. - I'm sorry.
- 你得把我抓起来 - 我很抱歉
Let's go.
咱们走吧
This is gonna sound strange.
我知道这听起来也许挺怪的
I'm glad it was you.
但是被你逮捕 我还挺开心的
Daniel. Want to come and help me unpack?
Daniel 想来帮忙拆包吗
There's a couple beer in it for you.
里面还有几瓶给你的啤酒
Tempting, but I got a thing tonight. Well, that's your loss, pal.
- 听着不错 但我今晚有别的事 - 好吧 那是你的损失 老兄
Tell you what, save me a cold one.
这样吧 给我留一瓶冰的
Nice place. You need to start locking your door, though.
地方很不错 但是你得开始锁门了
Everything's unpacked.
所有的东西都帮你拆包了
You did this all for me?
你们这是为了我?
Someone needed to take responsibility.
某人得学会承担责任
I'm gonna get you all keys, alright?
我会给你们每人配一把钥匙的 行了吧?
Guys...
伙计们...
Okay, tough guy. What would you do if I did this...
好吧 猛男 你会怎么应对 如果我做了...
Not bad.
不算糟
It's the reflexes of a jungle cat.
丛林猛猫的本能反应
Is that right?
是吗
- Yeah... - Yeah?
- 是啊... - 是吗
I can still see that skinny kid in his uniform.
那个穿着制服的羸弱青年仿佛还在我眼前
Never really fit him. Didn't fit any of us.
- 他怎么穿都不合身 - 咱们穿都不合身
All he wanted was to catch the bad guy.
他想要的一切只是抓住坏人
I should've seen it.
我该看到这一点的
You did. I pushed.
你看到了 是我推了你一把
I let you.
那是我让你推的
You ever worry it'll happen to you?
你会担心同样的事发生在自己身上吗
Every day.
每天都在担心
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入